Guide to the Human Service Employees Registration and Voter Education Fund (Human SERVE) records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XXIX: Press
  - News-Register (McMinnville, Oregon) (Box 37, Folder 1704)
  - The News Tribune (Washington) (Box 37, Folder 1705)
  - Newsweek (Box 37, Folder 1706)
  - New York Amsterdam News (Box 37, Folder 1707)
  - New York Daily News (Box 37, Folder 1708)
  - New York Law Journal (Box 37, Folder 1709)
  - NY Newsday (Box 37, Folder 1710)
  - NY Observer (Box 37, Folder 1711)
  - New York Post (Box 37, Folder 1712)
  - New York Press (Assorted) (Box 37, Folder 1713)
  - The New York Review of Books (Box 37, Folder 1714)
  - New York Times (All), 1980 (Box 38, Folder 1715)
  - New York Times (All), 1983 (Box 38, Folder 1716)
  - New York Times (National), 1984 (Box 38, Folder 1717)
  - New York Times (City & State), 1984 (Box 38, Folder 1718)
  - New York Times (All), 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1719)
  - New York Times (All), 1986 (Box 38, Folder 1720)
  - New York Times (National), 1987 (Box 38, Folder 1721)
  - New York Times (City & State), 1987 (Box 38, Folder 1722)
  - New York Times (City & State), 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1723)
  - New York Times (National), 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1724)
  - New York Times (City & State), 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1725)
  - New York Times (National), 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1726)
  - New York Times (National), 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1727)
  - New York Times (City & State), 1990 (Box 38, Folder 1728)
  - New York Times (All), 1991 (Box 38, Folder 1729)
  - New York Times (National), 1992 (Box 38, Folder 1730)
  - New York Times (City & State), 1992 (Box 38, Folder 1731)
  - New York Times (City & State), 1993 (Box 38, Folder 1732)
  - New York Times (National), 1993 (Box 38, Folder 1733)
  - New York Times (All), 1994 (Box 38, Folder 1734)
  - New York Times (All), 1995 (Box 38, Folder 1735)
  - New York Times (All), 1996 (Box 38, Folder 1736)
  - New York Times (All), 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 1737)
  - The New York Times Magazine (Box 38, Folder 1738)
  - New Yorker (Box 38, Folder 1739)
  - Nugget (Oregon) (Box 38, Folder 1740)
  - Oakland Tribune (Box 38, Folder 1741)
  - The Observer (La Grande, Oregon) (Box 38, Folder 1742)
  - Olympian (Washington) (Box 38, Folder 1743)
  - The Oregonian (Box 38, Folder 1744)
  - Our Town (Chicago Area Local) (Box 38, Folder 1745)
  - Pacifica News (Box 38, Folder 1746)
  - The Paperworker (Box 38, Folder 1747)
  - Parade Magazine (Box 38, Folder 1748)
  - People (Box 38, Folder 1749)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer (Box 38, Folder 1750)
  - Pioneer Press (Box 38, Folder 1751)
  - Pitt News (Box 38, Folder 1752)
  - Pittsburgh Post Gazette (Box 38, Folder 1753)
  - Piven and Cloward Articles (Box 38, Folder 1754)
  - Polemicist (Box 38, Folder 1755)
  - PS-Political Science & Politics (Box 38, Folder 1756)
  - Portland Press Herald (Box 38, Folder 1757)
  - Press-Telegram (Long Beach, CA) (Box 38, Folder 1758)
  - Providence Journal (Box 38, Folder 1759)
  - The Progressive (Box 38, Folder 1760)
  - Public Citizen (Box 38, Folder 1761)
  - Public Opinion (Box 38, Folder 1762)
  - Reader's Digest (Box 38, Folder 1763)
  - The Record (Box 38, Folder 1764)
  - Record (Pendleton, OR) (Box 38, Folder 1765)
  - Register Herald (Box 38, Folder 1766)
  - Register-Guard (Oregon) (Box 38, Folder 1767)
  - Reno Gazette-Journal (Box 38, Folder 1768)
  - Reporter (Box 38, Folder 1769)
  - Rocky Mountain News (Box 38, Folder 1770)
  - Roll Call (Box 38, Folder 1771)
  - Rolling Stone (Box 38, Folder 1772)
  - Sacramento Bee (Box 38, Folder 1773)
  - St. Paul Pioneer (Box 38, Folder 1774)
  - San Antonio Light (Box 38, Folder 1775)
  - The San Diego Union (Box 38, Folder 1776)
  - San Francisco Chronicle (Box 38, Folder 1777)
  - San Francisco Examiner (Box 38, Folder 1778)
  - San Jose Mercury News (Box 38, Folder 1779)
  - Sarasota Herald Tribune (Box 38, Folder 1780)
  - Seattle Post Intelligencer (Box 38, Folder 1781)
  - The Seattle Times (Box 38, Folder 1782)
  - Seventeen (Box 38, Folder 1783)
  - Shelter Force (Box 38, Folder 1784)
  - Sixty Minutes (Box 38, Folder 1785)
  - Eleanor Smeal Report (Box 38, Folder 1786)
  - Social Policy (Box 38, Folder 1787)
  - Southtown Economist (Box 38, Folder 1788)
  - Spokesman Review (Box 38, Folder 1789)
  - Spy Magazine (Box 38, Folder 1790)
  - Star-Ledger (Box 38, Folder 1791)
  - Star Tribune (Box 38, Folder 1792)
  - The State (Box 38, Folder 1793)
  - State Government News (Box 38, Folder 1794)
  - States Legislatures (Box 38, Folder 1795)
  - Staten Island Advance (Box 38, Folder 1796)
  - Staten Island Register (Box 38, Folder 1797)
  - The State Journal (Frankfort, KY) (Box 38, Folder 1798)
  - Statesman Journal (Box 38, Folder 1799)
  - Suburban/Chicago (Box 38, Folder 1800)
  - The Sun - Maryland (Box 38, Folder 1801)
  - Sun-Sentinel (South Florida, FL) (Box 38, Folder 1802)
  - Syracuse Herald-Journal (Box 38, Folder 1803)
  - Tacoma News Tribune (Box 38, Folder 1804)
  - Tallahassee Democrat (Box 38, Folder 1805)
  - Tampa Tribune (Box 38, Folder 1806)
  - Teacher Magazine (Box 38, Folder 1807)
  - Texas Observer (Box 38, Folder 1808)
  - TIME (Box 38, Folder 1809)
  - The Times Argus (Box 38, Folder 1810)
  - Times Herald Record (Box 38, Folder 1811)
  - Times-Picayune (Box 38, Folder 1812)
  - Times Union (Albany, NY) (Box 38, Folder 1813)
  - The Trentonian (Box 38, Folder 1814)
  - Trenton Times (Box 38, Folder 1815)
  - Tribune (Great Falls, MT) (Box 38, Folder 1816)
  - The Tribune (San Diego, CA) (Box 38, Folder 1817)
  - Tri-Cities Herald (Kennewick, WA) (Box 38, Folder 1818)
  - Union Bulletin, Walla Walla, WA (Box 39, Folder 1819)
  - United Press International (Box 39, Folder 1820)
  - USA Today (Box 39, Folder 1821)
  - Viewpoints (Box 39, Folder 1822)
  - Village Voice (Box 39, Folder 1823)
  - Virginian-Pilot/Ledger-Star (Box 39, Folder 1824)
  - Voter Research & Surveys (Box 39, Folder 1825)
  - Voting Rights Review (Box 39, Folder 1826)
  - Wall Street Journal (Box 39, Folder 1827)
  - Washington Post, 1983-1989 (Box 39, Folder 1828)
  - Washington Post, 1990-1998 (Box 39, Folder 1829)
  - Washington Times (Box 39, Folder 1830)
  - WBAI (Box 39, Folder 1831)
  - West Linn Tidings (West Linn, OR) (Box 39, Folder 1832)
  - The Westsider (Box 39, Folder 1833)
  - Why Americans Don't Vote Reviews (Box 39, Folder 1834)
  - The Wichita Eagle (Box 39, Folder 1835)
  - Whole Earth Review (Box 39, Folder 1836)
  - WINS (Box 39, Folder 1837)
  - Winston-Salem Journal (Box 39, Folder 1838)
  - Women's Day (Box 39, Folder 1839)
  - Woodstock Times (Box 39, Folder 1840)
  - World News Tonight (Box 39, Folder 1841)
- Series XXX: Voter Registration and Turnout Data
  - Human SERVE Publications, 1980-1997 (Box 39, Folder 1842)
  - Controversy with Curtis Gans (Box 39, Folder 1843)
  - Correspondence Memos, 1996-1997 (Box 39, Folder 1844)
  - Press/Resource Materials, 1984-1989 (Box 39, Folder 1845)
  - Press/Resource Materials, 1990-1993 (Box 39, Folder 1846)
  - Press/Resource Materials, 1995-1997 (Box 39, Folder 1847)
  - Press/Resource Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 1848)
  - Purging, 1996 (Box 39, Folder 1849)
  - Partisan Advantage (Box 39, Folder 1850)
- Series XXXI: Subjects
  - Absentee Ballots (Box 39, Folder 1851)
  - Adult Education Programs (Box 39, Folder 1852)
  - Agriculture Department Barriers (Box 39, Folder 1853)
  - Ballot Access News (Box 39, Folder 1854)
  - Walter Dean Burnham (Box 39, Folder 1855)
  - Thomas Cavanagh (Box 39, Folder 1856)
  - Christian Coalition (Box 39, Folder 1857)
  - Commission on National Elections (Box 39, Folder 1858)
  - Community Education (Box 39, Folder 1859)
  - Community Service Society Fundraiser (Box 39, Folder 1860)
  - Computerized Voter Rolls (Box 39, Folder 1861)
  - Constitution (Box 39, Folder 1862)
  - Corporate Voter Registration (Box 39, Folder 1863)
  - Day Care (Box 39, Folder 1864)
  - Deadwood (Box 39, Folder 1865)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1984-1987 (Box 39, Folder 1866)
  - Democratic National Committee, January 1988-May 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1867)
  - Democratic National Committee, June 1988 (Box 39, Folder 1868)
  - Democratic National Committee Task Force (Box 40, Folder 1869)
  - Democratic National Committee: National Lawyers Council Voter Action Project (Podesta), 1988 (Box 40, Folder 1870)
  - Democratic Convention, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 1871)
  - Democratic Platform, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 1872)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1989-1995 (Box 40, Folder 1873)
  - Department of Defense (Box 40, Folder 1874)
  - Disabilities (Box 40, Folder 1875)
  - Dukakis Campaign (Box 40, Folder 1876)
  - Election Day Registration, 1977-1986 (Box 40, Folder 1877)
  - Election Day Registration, 1987-1994 (Box 40, Folder 1878)
  - Election Day Identification, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 1879)
  - Electronic Voting, 1985-1989 (Box 40, Folder 1880)
  - Electronic Voting, 1990-1991 (Box 40, Folder 1881)
  - Felons Voting (Box 40, Folder 1882)
  - Mervin Field (Box 40, Folder 1883)
  - Film (Box 40, Folder 1884)
  - Food Banks (Box 40, Folder 1885)
  - Forms (Combined & Amended & Welfare) #1 (Box 40, Folder 1886)
  - Forms (Combined & Amended & Welfare) #2 (Box 40, Folder 1887)
  - Form Redesign (Box 40, Folder 1888)
  - Franking Privilege (Box 40, Folder 1889)
  - Fraud, 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 1890)
  - Fraud, 1987-1989 (Box 40, Folder 1891)
  - Fraud, 1993-1994 (Box 40, Folder 1892)
  - Fraud, January 1995-June 1995 (Box 40, Folder 1893)
  - Fraud, July 1995 (Box 41, Folder 1894)
  - Fraud, August 1995-November 1995 (Box 41, Folder 1895)
  - Fraud, 1996-1998 (Box 41, Folder 1896)
  - Freedom of Information Act (Box 41, Folder 1897)
  - Mark Green (Box 41, Folder 1898)
  - Greenhalgh (Box 41, Folder 1899)
  - Lani Guinier (Box 41, Folder 1900)
  - Jane Frank Harman (Box 41, Folder 1901)
  - Harvard/ABC Symposium (Box 41, Folder 1902)
  - Hazen, Don (Box 41, Folder 1903)
  - High Schools Project (Box 41, Folder 1904)
  - Hightower (Box 41, Folder 1905)
  - Homeless Voting Rights (Box 41, Folder 1906)
  - Hospitals (Box 41, Folder 1907)
  - Immigration (Box 41, Folder 1908)
  - Initiative (Box 41, Folder 1909)
  - Interface (Box 41, Folder 1910)
  - International (Box 41, Folder 1911)
  - Jesse Jackson (Box 41, Folder 1912)
  - Sonia Jarvis (Box 41, Folder 1913)
  - Jewish Groups (Box 41, Folder 1914)
  - Jury Duty/Voter Registration (Box 41, Folder 1915)
  - Kennedy School of Government (Box 41, Folder 1916)
  - King, Coretta Scott (Box 41, Folder 1917)
  - Latino Involvement (Box 41, Folder 1918)
  - Leadership Council (Box 41, Folder 1919)
  - Literacy (Box 41, Folder 1920)
  - Mail-In Registration (Box 41, Folder 1921)
  - Mobility (Box 41, Folder 1922)
  - Montjoy, Robert (Box 41, Folder 1923)
  - Nadar, Ralph (Box 41, Folder 1924)
  - Our Vote Counts (Box 41, Folder 1925)
  - Podesta (Box 41, Folder 1926)
  - Polls (Box 41, Folder 1927)
  - Poverty (Box 41, Folder 1928)
  - Private Agencies/General (Box 41, Folder 1929)
  - Pro-Choice Strategy (Box 41, Folder 1930)
  - Public Housing (Box 41, Folder 1931)
  - Redistricting (Box 41, Folder 1932)
  - Republican Party, 1984-1987 (Box 41, Folder 1933)
  - Republican Party, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 1934)
  - Republican Party, 1989-1992 (Box 41, Folder 1935)
  - Research- Gender Gap (Box 42, Folder 1936)
  - Research- General (Box 42, Folder 1937)
  - Research- Rosenstone (Box 42, Folder 1938)
  - Research- Voter Motivation (Box 42, Folder 1939)
  - Joel Rogers (Box 42, Folder 1940)
  - Schwerner, Chaney, Goodman, February 1967-May 1989 (Box 42, Folder 1941)
  - Schwerner, Chaney, Goodman, 1989-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1942)
  - Social Security Numbers (Box 42, Folder 1943)
  - Supreme Court (Box 42, Folder 1944)
  - Telephone Book (Box 42, Folder 1945)
  - Uniform Law Commissioners (Box 42, Folder 1946)
  - United States Postal Service (Box 42, Folder 1947)
  - Utilities (Box 42, Folder 1948)
  - Voluntary Agency Questionnaire (Box 42, Folder 1949)
  - Why Americans Don't Vote (Box 42, Folder 1950)
  - Why Americans Still Don't Vote (Box 42, Folder 1950a)
  - Ray Wolfinger (Box 42, Folder 1951)
  - Women, 1983-1990 (Box 42, Folder 1952)
  - Women, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 1953)
  - Youth/Campus (Box 42, Folder 1954)
  - Frank Zappa (Box 42, Folder 1955)
- Series XXXII: Chronologies (Staff Correspondence Files)
  - Support Letters to Human SERVE (Box 42, Folder 1956)
  - Michelle Billies, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 1957)
  - Michelle Billies, February 1996-March 1996 (Box 42, Folder 1958)
  - Michelle Billies, April 1996 (Box 42, Folder 1959)
  - Michelle Billies, May 1996 (Box 42, Folder 1960)
  - Michelle Billies, June 1996-September 1996 (Box 42, Folder 1961)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 1962)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1987-February 1987 (Box 42, Folder 1963)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, March 1987-June 1987 (Box 42, Folder 1964)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, July 1987-September 1987 (Box 42, Folder 1965)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, October 1987-December 1987 (Box 42, Folder 1966)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1988-February 1988 (Box 42, Folder 1967)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, March 1988-April 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1968)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, May 1988-June 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1969)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, July 1988-August 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1970)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, September 1988-October 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1971)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, November 1988-December 1988 (Box 43, Folder 1972)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1989-February 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1973)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, March 1989-April 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1974)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, May 1989-June 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1975)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, July 1989-August 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1976)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, September 1989-October 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1977)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, November 1989-December 1989 (Box 43, Folder 1978)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1990-April 1990 (Box 43, Folder 1979)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, May 1990-December 1990 (Box 43, Folder 1980)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1991-June 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1981)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, July 1991-December 1991 (Box 43, Folder 1982)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1992-April 1992 (Box 43, Folder 1983)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, May 1992-December 1992 (Box 43, Folder 1984)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 1985)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1994-May 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1986)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, June 1994-December 1994 (Box 43, Folder 1987)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1995-June 1995 (Box 43, Folder 1988)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, July 1995-December 1995 (Box 43, Folder 1989)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1996-May 1996 (Box 43, Folder 1990)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, June 1996-December 1996 (Box 44, Folder 1991)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow, January 1997-June 1999 (Box 44, Folder 1992)
  - Marilyn Clement, February 1989-August 1989 (Box 44, Folder 1993)
  - Marilyn Clement, September 1989-December 1989 (Box 44, Folder 1994)
  - Marilyn Clement, January 1990-March 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1995)
  - Jim Conley, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 1996)
  - Jim Conley, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 1997)
  - Linda Davidoff, January 1988-February 1988 (Box 44, Folder 1998)
  - Linda Davidoff, March 1988-May 1988 (Box 44, Folder 1999)
  - Linda Davidoff, June 1988 (Box 44, Folder 2000)
  - Linda Davidoff, July 1988 (Box 44, Folder 2001)
  - Linda Davidoff, August 1988-September 1988 (Box 44, Folder 2002)
  - Rebekah Evenson, August 1994-October 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2003)
  - Rebekah Evenson, November 1994-December 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2004)
  - Rebekah Evenson, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 2005)
  - Margaret Hart, July 1986-August 1986 (Box 44, Folder 2006)
  - Margaret Hart, September 1986-December 1986 (Box 44, Folder 2007)
  - Margaret Hart, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 2008)
  - John Henry (Box 44, Folder 2009)
  - Deborah Karpatkin, February 1989-May 1989 (Box 44, Folder 2010)
  - Deborah Karpatkin, June 1989-December 1989 (Box 44, Folder 2011)
  - Deborah Karpatkin, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 2012)
  - Susan Kotcher, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 2013)
  - Susan Kotcher, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2014)
  - Jordan Moss (Box 44, Folder 2015)
  - David Plotkin, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 2016)
  - David Plotkin, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 2017)
  - David Plotkin, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 2018)
  - Catherine Willis, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 2019)
- Series XXXIII: Board/Staff
  - Louise Altman (Box 45, Folder 2020)
  - Beatrice Beasley (Box 45, Folder 2021)
  - Margot Beutler (Box 45, Folder 2022)
  - Michelle Billies (Box 45, Folder 2023)
  - Sara Borden (Box 45, Folder 2024)
  - Frances Brown (Box 45, Folder 2025)
  - Lewis Carter (Box 45, Folder 2026)
  - Jo-Anne Chasnow (Box 45, Folder 2027)
  - Marilyn Clement (Box 45, Folder 2028)
  - Ron Daniels (Box 45, Folder 2029)
  - Linda Davidoff (Box 45, Folder 2030)
  - Rebekah Evenson (Box 45, Folder 2031)
  - Barbara Facher (Box 45, Folder 2032)
  - Gretchen Harper Flatau (Box 45, Folder 2033)
  - Joe Gardner (Box 45, Folder 2034)
  - Margaret Hart (Box 45, Folder 2035)
  - Hulbert James (Box 45, Folder 2036)
  - Deborah Karpatkin (Box 45, Folder 2037)
  - Suzin Kim (Box 45, Folder 2038)
  - Susan Kotcher (Box 45, Folder 2039)
  - Natalie Langston-Davis (Box 45, Folder 2040)
  - Lafe Larson (Box 45, Folder 2041)
  - Robin Leeds (Box 45, Folder 2042)
  - Dawn Lipscomb (Box 45, Folder 2043)
  - Martin Ludlow (Box 45, Folder 2044)
  - Jordan Moss (Box 45, Folder 2045)
  - Immanuel Ness (Box 45, Folder 2046)
  - Susan Philips (Box 45, Folder 2047)
  - Sheila Pugh (Box 45, Folder 2048)
  - Jeri Rasmussen (Box 45, Folder 2049)
  - Brian Sherman (Box 45, Folder 2050)
  - Irene Susmano (Box 45, Folder 2051)
  - Linda McDonald Thomas (Box 45, Folder 2052)
  - Wayne Thompson (Box 45, Folder 2053)
  - Eartha Warring (Box 45, Folder 2054)
  - Cindy Williams (Box 45, Folder 2055)
  - Catherine Willis (Box 45, Folder 2056)
  - Lynda Wright (Box 45, Folder 2057)
  - Emergency Campaign, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 2058)
  - Board Meeting, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 2059)
  - Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2060)
  - Staff Memos, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2061)
  - Internal Fundraising, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2062)
  - Organization Assessment: Interface, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2063)
  - Board Member Biographies, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 2064)
  - Staff Meeting, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 2065)
  - To the Board, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 2066)
  - Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 2067)
  - Board Meetings, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 2068)
  - National Staff Meeting, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 2069)
  - Staff Meetings, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 2070)
  - Organization Evaluation: Hamilton, Rabinowitz, and Altschuler, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 2071)
  - Staff Memos, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 2072)
  - Staff Memos, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 2073)
  - Staff Meetings, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 2074)
  - Board, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 2075)
  - Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 46, Folder 2076)
  - Board Meetings, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 2077)
  - Staff Meetings, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 2078)
  - Staff Memos, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 2079)
  - Financial Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 2080)
  - Staff Memos, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 2081)
  - New Board, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 2082)
  - Staff Retreat, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 2083)
  - Board Meetings, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 2084)
  - Staff Meetings, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 2085)
  - Staff Meetings, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 2086)
  - Board Correspondence, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 2087)
  - Executive Committee, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 2088)
  - Staff Memos, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 2089)
  - Board Meeting, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 2090)
  - Board Correspondence, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 2091)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 2092)
  - Staff Meetings, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 2093)
  - Board Meeting, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 2094)
  - Staff Meetings, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 2095)
  - Board Meetings, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 2096)
  - Board Meeting, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 2097)
  - Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 2098)
  - Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 2099)
  - Board, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 2100)
  - Board List, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 2101)
  - Board Meeting, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 2102)
- Series XXXIV: Internal Administration/Operations
  - Intentionally eliminated (Box 46, Folder 2103-2105)
  - Compliance D.C. Filings Human SERVE Campaign (Box 46, Folder 2106)
  - Compliance Lobbying Guidelines 501(c)(3) IRS Information (Box 46, Folder 2107)
  - Compliance Legal/IRS, 1983-1988 (Box 46, Folder 2108)
  - Compliance Department of Labor, 1992-1997 (Box 46, Folder 2109)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 2110)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 2111)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 2112)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 2113)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 2114)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 2115)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 2116)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 2117)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 2118)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 2119)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 2120)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 2121)
  - Taxes/Audits 990, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 2122)
  - Taxes/Audits 990,497, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 2123)
  - Taxes/Audits, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 2124)
  - Financial Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 47, Folder 2125)
  - Financial Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 47, Folder 2126)
  - Financial Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 2127)
  - Financial Reports Summaries, 1984-1994 (Box 47, Folder 2128)
  - 1099's, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 2129)
  - 1099's, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 2130)
  - 1099's, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 2131)
  - 1099's W-Z's, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 2132)
  - 1099's, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 2133)
  - 1099's, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 2134)
  - 1099's, 1991 & 1992 (Box 47, Folder 2135)
  - 1099's, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 2136)
  - 1099's, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 2137)
  - 1099's, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 2138)
  - 1099's, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 2139)
  - 1099's, 1998 (Box 47, Folder 2140)
  - Human SERVE Lawsuit in California: Judge Newman's Positive Decision, 1980s (Box 47, Folder Video: #1:)
  - Various short pieces: WNBC & CNN (18 minutes only), 1988 (Box 47, Folder Video: #2:)
  - CNN - Crier & Co.: Prior to President Bush's Veto: Frances Fox Piven, June 24, 1992 (Box 47, Folder Video: #3:)
  - CNN Veto of NVRA by President Bush: Various commentators, US Senator McConnell, July 1992 (Box 47, Folder Video: #4:)
  - MacNeil/Lehrer Newshour: Post-veto of NVRA by President Bush -- Congressman Al Swift, League of Women Voters, etc., July 1992 (Box 47, Folder Video: #5:)
  - House Republicans Livingston & Gingrich discussing NVRA - HR2, 2/4/93 (Box 47, Folder Video: #6:)
  - Clinton Signs the National Voter Registration Act (Cloward & Piven), May 20, 1993 (Box 47, Folder Video: #7:)
  - CSPAN Washington Journal: President of League of Women Voters, Early 1995 (Box 47, Folder Video: #8:)
  - CSPAN National Voter Registration Act: 10/15/96 (Box 47, Folder Video: #9:)
  - League of Women Voters/Human SERVE/NAACP (Box 47, Folder Video: #9:)